<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MerseyTrains Live</string>
    <string name="timetables">Timetables</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="select_number">Select Number</string>
    <string name="search">Search. . .</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">tab</string>
    <string name="app_description">With MerseyTrains Live you can view, search and favourite any route or service on the MerseyRail network. Press a station or train on the live Map to view schedules and use the Timetables tab to search service times between stations. You can view and remove favourites via the Favourites tab, and add new ones from your journey search.</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">MerseyTrains Live hereby grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable licence to use the App for your personal, non-commercial use and only on an Apple or Android device (“Device”) as permitted by the applicable Platform Terms and in accordance with these App Terms (“User Licence”). All other rights in the App are reserved by Drinkaware. In the event of your breach of these App Terms we will be entitled to terminate the User Licence immediately. You acknowledge that your agreement with your mobile network provider (“Mobile Provider”) will apply to your use of the App. You acknowledge that you may be charged by the Mobile Provider for data services while using certain features of the App or any such third party charges as may arise and you accept responsibility for such charges. If you are not the bill payer for the Device being used to access the App, you will be assumed to have received permission from the bill payer for using the App. You acknowledge that where you use services provided by Apple or Google (or any other third parties) in connection with your use of the App, you will be subject to Apple’s, Google’s (or the applicable third party’s) terms and conditions and privacy policy and you should ensure that you have read such terms.</string>
</resources>