<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MerseyTrains Live</string>
    <string name="timetables">Timetables</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="select_number">Select Number</string>
    <string name="search">Search. . .</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">tab</string>
    <string name="change">Change Here</string>
    <string name="app_description">With MerseyTrains Live you can view, search and favourite any route or service on the MerseyRail network. Press a station or train on the live Map to view schedules and use the Timetables tab to search service times between stations. You can view and remove favourites via the Favourites tab, and add new ones from your journey search.</string>
    <string name="conditions">Our sites are made available free of charge. We do not guarantee that MerseyTrains Live will be always available. We retain the right to withdraw or restrict availability to some or all parts of the app however we will try to get reasonable notice of changes to availability.
We, as a collective, are the owner of all intellectual property rights in our app, this work is protected by copyright laws and treaties around the world- all such rights are reserved including the right to pursue legal action upon infractions of copyright law.
Our status, and that of any identified contributors including trainlive?? Googlemaps??, as authors of content on our app must always be acknowledged when the app is referenced.
You must not use any part of the content of our app for commercial purposes without obtaining the correct licenses from trainlive, googlemaps and our permission first.
The content of our app is provided for general purpose only, it is not intended to amount to advice for which you should rely on. Although we take every effort to update the information on our app promptly, we make no guarantees that the content our pap is accurate, complete or up to date. </string>
</resources>